Charles and Ray were a team. They were husband and wife.
Charles and Ray waren een team. Zij waren man en vrouw.
Despite the New York Times' and Vanity Fair's best efforts recently,
Ondanks de recente uitspraken van de New York Times en Vanity Fair,
they're not brothers. (Laughter)
waren zij geen broers.
And they were a lot of fun.
En ze waren ontzettend leuk.
You know, Ray was the one who wore the ampersands in the family.
Ray was degene in de familie die de ampersands droeg.
(Laughter)
(Gelach)
We are going to focus on Charles today, because it is Charles' 100th birthday.
We richten ons vandaag op Charles, want het is zijn honderdste verjaardag.
But when I speak of him, I'm really speaking of both of them as a team.
Maar wanneer ik het over Charles heb, spreek ik eigenlijk over beiden als team.
Here's Charles when he was three. So he would be 100 this June.
Dit is Charles toen hij drie was. In juni dit jaar zou hij dus honderd zijn geworden.
We have a lot of cool celebrations that we're going to do.
We hebben een hoop leuke feesten gepland.
The thing about their work
Typisch voor hun werk
is that most people come to the door of furniture --
is dat de meeste mensen via de meubels binnenkomen –
I suspect you probably recognize this chair
Ik vermoed dat je deze stoel waarschijnlijk herkent,